<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>/blog.rss</link>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor: TIM Group</title>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD HTML 4.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40/loose.dtd"&gt;
&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.timgroup.com/"&gt;&lt;img alt="Tim-group" class="sponsor" src="/sponsors/image/400x150/tim-group.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TIMGroup is proud to sponsor BarCamp London 9.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.timgroup.com/"&gt;TIMGroup&lt;/a&gt; develops and operates secure, scalable browser-based applications that enable service providers and investors to improve their trading and investment returns – and enhance their relationships across the global financial landscape. Their teams in London, New York, Boston and Hong Kong work with over 500 institutions, from global investment banks to regional niche firms, and over 150 institutional investors, including major hedge funds, traditional money managers and funds of hedge funds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their development teams are agile and we work in an office that is almost solid whiteboards.  If you'd like to work in the financial sphere but still get to use cutting edge techniques, plus go home at a reasonable hour, visit them at &lt;a href="http://www.timgroup.com/careers"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.timgroup.com/careers"&gt;http://www.timgroup.com/careers&lt;/a&gt; or talk to one of them at BarCamp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 16:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>/blog/sponsor-tim-group.rss</link>
      <guid>/blog/sponsor-tim-group.rss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor: TechSmith</title>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD HTML 4.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40/loose.dtd"&gt;
&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://techsmith.com"&gt;&lt;img alt="Techsmith" class="sponsor" src="/sponsors/image/400x150/techsmith.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our next wonderful sponsor is TechSmith.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TechSmith is the name behind &lt;a href="http://www.techsmith.com/camtasia/"&gt;Camtasia Studio&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.techsmith.com/screen-capture.asp"&gt;Snagit&lt;/a&gt;, two of the most popular screencasting/capture applications for Windows and Mac.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People everywhere use their products to grab images and record content straight off their computer screens to create dynamic presentations and screencasts. With their products, people communicate more effectively and create interest with engaging visuals and sharp videos that grab attention and keep it. TechSmith develops and updates their innovative software every day and plans to continue expanding their existing products to support the Mac platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’d like to thank TechSmith for their continuing support of BarCamps around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 16:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>/blog/sponsor-techsmith.rss</link>
      <guid>/blog/sponsor-techsmith.rss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor: Potato</title>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD HTML 4.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40/loose.dtd"&gt;
&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://p.ota.to/"&gt;&lt;img alt="Potato" class="sponsor" src="/sponsors/image/400x150/potato.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet another generous sponsor for BarCamp London 9: Potato.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2010, &lt;a href="http://p.ota.to/"&gt;Potato&lt;/a&gt; is a rapidly-growing creator of complex web apps, working with companies like Google and PayPal from London, Bristol and Amsterdam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Potato plays home to a multi-disciplined team of webdev experts, tackling projects that range from complex marketing initiatives like &lt;a href="http://p.ota.to/work/google-engage/"&gt;Google Engage&lt;/a&gt; and massive-scale &lt;a href="http://p.ota.to/work/youtube/"&gt;YouTube channels&lt;/a&gt;, to fun, interesting diversions like our &lt;a href="http://p.ota.to/work/getfavicon/"&gt;getFavicon tool&lt;/a&gt; (which serves over 100 req/sec).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We love working in the cloud, and as such develop almost solely using services like Google App Engine. As Potato continues to grow we’re also on the hunt for developers to &lt;a href="http://p.ota.to/jobs/"&gt;join our team&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 12:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>/blog/sponsor-potato.rss</link>
      <guid>/blog/sponsor-potato.rss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor: CoderStack</title>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD HTML 4.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40/loose.dtd"&gt;
&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coderstack.co.uk/"&gt;&lt;img alt="Coderstack" class="sponsor" src="/sponsors/image/400x150/coderstack.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next sponsor for BarCamp London 9 is CoderStack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coderstack.co.uk/"&gt;CoderStack&lt;/a&gt; is the UK's leading specialist job board for Software&lt;br&gt;
Developers. They focus purely on companies hiring directly (no&lt;br&gt;
recruiters) and encourage companies to write meaningful and&lt;br&gt;
interesting job ads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 10:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>/blog/sponsor-coderstack.rss</link>
      <guid>/blog/sponsor-coderstack.rss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor: TwentyFourNine</title>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD HTML 4.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40/loose.dtd"&gt;
&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://twentyfournine.co.uk/"&gt;&lt;img alt="Twentyfournine" class="sponsor" src="/sponsors/image/400x150/twentyfournine.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next to join our growing list of wonderful sponsors for BarCamp London 9 is TwentyFourNine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://twentyfournine.co.uk/"&gt;TwentyFourNine&lt;/a&gt; is a tiny web development outfit specialising in web apps. Founded in 2009, it is the brainchild of London resident Ruben Arakelyan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They have worked with lots of individuals and organisations large and small, some well-known, some not so much, from universities to record labels to create websites and web apps ranging from educational to entertainment. They are also behind the popular net:Base web app for netball teams and leagues as well as other commercial and open source tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are always interested in working with other talented people to create amazing things, so why not come up and say hello any time during the two days?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are proud to sponsor BarCamp London for the first time in 2011 and will be providing you with lunch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 09:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>/blog/sponsor-twentyfournine.rss</link>
      <guid>/blog/sponsor-twentyfournine.rss</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
